Big brother!
The sun's up! Time to wake up!
You'll be late for school
if you don't get up now!
Yeah...
Okay, got it.
Hurry and come downstairs.
That was a good night's sleep.
It wasn't a dream?
Sis, breakfast is ready.
Sorry, Iori.
I overslept again.
Don't worry about it.
I know you must be tired.
Take your time.
You can drink this before you go.
Oh, I forgot the sugar.
Thank you.
I'll help myself.
Oh, was it too hot?
No, it's fine.
Good.
What's this, Yoshifumi?
Huh?
Talking to a friend?
I-It's nothing!
Don't peek over my shoulder!
Are you heading out, Himeko?
Shouldn't that be obvious?
That's cold.
You'll never get a boyfriend like that.
Scary!
Morning, Taichi.
You look tired.
You're always fired up in the morning.
That's because I don't stay up late
watching pro wrestling like you.
Oh.
Morning!
Inaban!
Oh, you guys came to school together today?
No, no.
We just ran into each other.
Oh?
Yui and Aoki, morning!
Morning.
It's way too hot for the end of September.
This is just how I like it.
Probably because you can't
even feel the seasons change.
Right?
Huh?
S-Sure...
At Yamaboshi Academy,
the private school we attend,
every student is required to join a club.
However, every organization is bound
to have a few rogue elements.
For example, take me,
a diehard pro wrestling fan
who put the Pro Wrestling Society,
which doesn't exist, as my club of choice.
For example,
take Kiriyama Yui, who goes
googly-eyed over anything cute
and applied to join the Fancy Club,
which had already closed down.
For example, take Aoki Yoshifumi,
who tried to join the Player's Club
because he believed the rumors
that there was such a thing.
For example,
take Nagase Iori, who figured that choosing
one club out of so many would be too hard,
and that the new and exciting option
would be to leave the decision to chance,
so she let her homeroom
teacher pick for her.
For example,
take Inaba Himeko, who
joined the Computer Club
but immediately got in a
spat with the president,
so she chose to take a different path.
Huh? You're the only one here, Inaba?
That should be obvious.
Long story short,
five first-years with nowhere else to go
joined together to form
the Student Cultural Society.
Or StuCS for short.
Taichi, do you have a topic for the
next edition of the StuCS paper?
You bet!
The title is "The History of Brainbuster
Drop Methods in Pro Wrestling."
Most people believe that
the Brainbuster involves
dropping the opponent on his back,
but originally, it was about dropping
the opponent on his head...
Zip it.
Er, you're the one who asked.
I only wanted to know if you had a topic.
I don't recall asking for any
elaboration upon said topic.
I don't want to hear it, either.
You never mince words.
'Sup! Sorry about being late!
Oh, it's just Taichi and Inaban?
Yeah, Kiriyama and Aoki
haven't shown up yet.
Lame, I sprinted up the stairs for nothing.
Iori...
Hm?
I don't see a problem.
You realize I'm in this room.
120 yen for every peek.
You're charging money?
But that's a pretty reasonable price.
What's your next topic, Nagase?
Yup, I've been thinking about
what's missing from the StuCS paper,
and I concluded that we need to add
a sexy and dangerous element!
Nobody's reading our paper for the thrills.
It can't hurt to spice
things up once in a while.
So Inaban, go for the sexy angle this time.
Don't ask an innocent high school
girl to write something erotic.
I'll write the article.
You just have to model
for a couple sexy shots.
Over my dead body!
Besides, you're the prettier one.
Wouldn't this be right up your alley?
Nuh-uh!
I'm more like an idol who's
not supposed to show any skin.
When we need something more sensual,
we turn to you.
Sensual?
I don't think boys in high
school are looking for that.
Wait, they might prefer a little maturity.
Then let's ask one of those
boys in high school.
M-Me?
Yup.
Which one of us would
you rather see naked?
Y-You want me to pick?
Well...
Since I'm representing
every boy in high school,
the answer would be both.
3:55 PM.
Yaegashi Taichi demands that
two female club members strip.
Huh?
Did you take that down, Inaban?
Of course.
This will go in the editorial notes.
I-I know I already said it,
so I can't take it back,
but can you at least
leave my name out of it?
Uh, please leave my name out.
Um...
What's wrong?
Well, we figured it would be a good
idea to talk to someone else.
I guess...
But now that we're here, it's like...
It's going to take a lot
of courage to say this.
Spit it out!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
You see, last night...
Our souls traded places!
Huh?
I'm saying that Yui and I switched places!
Like you see in manga!
Oh, overhead chop.
The punch line wasn't worth the set-up.
That wasn't a joke!
I'm being totally serious!
I'm more shocked
by the fact that Inaba hits
people for making bad jokes.
Did you escape to the world of dreams
after getting shot down
by Yui too many times?
That would make sense.
Since you keep asking Yui out
and she just ignores you.
That's not what this is about!
The same thing happened to Yui.
Right?
Yeah.
Yesterday, I woke up in
the middle of the night
and found myself in a
completely unfamiliar room.
When I looked in the mirror,
I saw Yui's face and panicked.
Next thing I knew, I was myself again.
That's what happened to me.
I thought it was just a bad dream,
so I hid under the covers.
When I opened my eyes again,
everything was back to normal.
That couldn't have been real!
Huh?
Yeah, it definitely wasn't real!
Aoki! Don't make me part
of your creepy fantasies!
You're turning on me?!
That had to be a nightmare!
So we had the same nightmare
in which we happened to switch
bodies at the same time,
and everything that was moved around
in your room when I panicked
was also moved around in the real world?
That's what happens when a string
of coincidences coincide!
Did that make sense to you?
More or less.
In other words, it was a miracle!
Besides, why would it be you and me?!
Well, you could chalk it up to
fate or karma from a past life.
So we should start going out!
How did he arrive at that conclusion?
This is why I can't stand you!
Iori!
That creep is making stuff up!
Right. There, there.
You don't have to be so mean about it.
God, this is making no sense at all!
The two of you need to cool off a bit!
Okay, but...
It doesn't make any sense to us either.
Ah!
I left my notebook in the classroom!
Don't cut me off in the middle of a thought!
It's no biggie.
So can I go grab it?
You're in charge here.
Don't ask me for permission.
We can continue this later!
Iori is the only person
who can give Inaba fits.
Iori-chan was trying to
be considerate, I guess?
Or maybe she's just clueless?
The problem is that you never know
when she's doing it on purpose.
Well, why don't we have tea now?
I'll make some for Nagase.
Yeah, you're...
Huh?
I was...
My voice?
No way...
This is...
Th-These are...
Are these... those?
It's my first time touching them.
But these are a girl's...
A woman's b-words?
Nagase-san, what are you doing?
Nagase-san?
Nagase?
Nagase-san, what are you doing?
U-Um...
Want me to help?
Huh?
It's more effective when someone
else fondles them for you.
In many ways.
N-No, thanks.
I'll be fine.
No need to be shy.
I'm very good with my hands.
L-Let's calm down, Fujishima.
We can talk this through.
Yes, let's talk...
...with our bodies!
B-Bodies?!
Taichi!
Me?!
Yaegashi-kun?!
Fujishima-san, I need
Taichi... Er, scratch that.
I need me... That's not it either.
Sorry, but I need Nagase Iori for something.
This is an emergency, so we're leaving.
We're busy right now!
I can't deny that it was about to get busy,
but please let me go, Fujishima!
See? Taichi says, I mean...
Nagase says to let her go!
The two of you sound kind of strange.
Anyway, you need to give me a good reason
before I let you take Nagase-san!
Just let go!
Fine, then!
Stop!
N-Not my sides!
H-Hey, Nagase.
You're Nagase, right?
You're in my body right now,
so don't do anything weird!
Let's just run away!
That was spooky.
I was looking for my notebook,
when all of a sudden, I
was back in the club room.
Everyone was calling me Taichi.
I freaked out and ran away.
So Aoki and Kiriyama
were telling the truth.
What is it this time?
Looks like Taichi and I traded places.
Isn't it rare to see a
genuine laugh from Taichi?
Usually, there's an edge of some sort.
True.
He's pretty good looking,
so he'd be popular with the
girls if he laughed more often.
Is my normal laugh really that bad?
Who gives a damn about your laugh?!
You just hurt your hand, didn't you?
Why you...
Shut up!
Inaban's really enjoying herself.
I got it.
What probably happened
was that Taichi mumbled one
of his signature one-liners,
so she was going to respond
with violence, as per the norm,
but he looks like Iori-chan now!
Which is why she stopped herself.
Pretty sad when Aoki gets
to sound condescending.
But I've never seen Inaba look so happy.
Don't think I'll forget this, Tai—
Inaban, you were about to
call Nagase Iori "Taichi."
That's because you guys are
putting on such a weird act.
Do you really think that Taichi's
capable of imitating me so well?
Inaba, I know that it's hard to
believe, but you have to trust me.
I'm Yaegashi Taichi.
Yui, Aoki, what do you think?
I'm positive that Taichi and
Iori-chan have switched places.
Don't you agree, Yui?
I hate to admit it, but I agree.
Oh?
Which means you're admitting
that we also traded places?
Yes.
I mean, after seeing Iori
and Taichi like this...
Still, shouldn't you be
a little more skeptical?
Well, once you've experienced the
switch, it's like, so that's it?
I'm getting a headache.
I'll ask you one more time.
You guys aren't fooling around
or anything like that?
Iori and Taichi have really switched bodies?
Yeah.
Which means you should know information
only Taichi would know, right?
Yeah, you can ask me anything.
I expect an answer in a split second.
Got it.
What's the title of the last adult
film that Taichi borrowed from Aoki?!
Big Jugged High School Gi—
Wait!
How could you ask that question?!
You don't even know the
answer to that question!
That doesn't matter.
Aoki can verify your answer.
Well, Taichi?
What's the answer?
Uh...
Big jugs, huh?
Uh, Inaba-san?
Could you let me whisper
the answer in Aoki's ear?
Well, Aoki?
That was the correct answer, Captain Inaba!
And I also got to hear Iori-chan
talk dirty in the process!
Wait, did I just get hosed?
Now that we've established that both of
the male club members like big jugs,
I'll find out if this is really Iori.
I-Is Inaba using this verification process
to get revenge for making fun of her?
I need to make sure I never
get on Inaba's bad side.
Wait!
I-Inaba!
Is that true?!
It's true.
But I guess that's what
it means to grow up.
What did Inaba-chan just tell her?
So you've switched bodies.
I guess it's true.
But if I compare the likelihood of Taichi
reacting in such an animated fashion
to the likelihood of two
people swapping bodies,
the latter is easier to swallow.
How am I supposed to
interpret that statement?
So, what are you going to do next?
Hm, what to do?
Aoki, Kiriyama, how long were
you in each other's bodies?
Thirty or forty minutes, I think.
Is time a factor?
Or mayb—
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
We're back to normal!
Seriously?
I have a feeling that it was all a dream.
Well, let's just say that
it's been a strange day.
I don't get it.
Was this a one day phenomenon?
Or something that only
happens to the four of you?
Anyway, we probably don't want
to mention this to anyone else.
No point in making our families worry.
Yeah, I doubt anyone would believe us.
Was this really a one day thing?
Hey, welcome home.
I'm home.
Hey, Himeko.
You're home?
Isn't that obvious?
What's wrong?
You look out of sorts.
Nothing's wrong.
This is how I always look.
Sis, are you okay?
You didn't look too good this morning.
Oh, I'm fine.
I just didn't get enough sleep.
Nothing you need to worry about.
Hello?
Oh, Mom?
Oh, you're gonna be late?
It's fine. I already ate.
Don't push yourself too hard.
Bye.
Big brother!
Oh, are you on your way home?
Yeah, I had a meeting that ran late.
I'm exhausted now.
Sounds like you had a rough day.
Want some ice cream?
Big brother, you should quit spoiling me.
I'm in fifth grade now!
You don't want any?
I do.
Did three people switch bodies this time?
What does a little-known plant
have to do with anything?
We can't wait until something goes wrong!
That's not who I am.